<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="true" translatedname="English">
  <!--override-->
  <entityname.alienblood>Alien Blood</entityname.alienblood>
  <entitydescription.alienbloodmod>Blood extracted from the body of a native species of Europa can be further processed into Blood products to treat blood loss. It can also be further purified into genes using therapeutics at the research bench.</entitydescription.alienbloodmod>
  <entitydescription.mudraptorshellmod>Velociraptor carapace fragment. Can be disenchanted into Exotic Matter and Velociraptor Headgear</entitydescription.mudraptorshellmod>
  <entityname.mudraptorshell_head>Velociraptor Headgear</entityname.mudraptorshell_head>
  <entitydescription.mudraptorshell_head>A small fragment of Velociraptor's carapace, I don't know which part of Velociraptor it is.</entitydescription.mudraptorshell_head>
  <entityname.exotic_matter>Exotic matter</entityname.exotic_matter>
  <!--entity-->
  <entityname.Wf_SaltedFish>Salted Fish Sword</entityname.Wf_SaltedFish>
  <entitydescription.Wf_SaltedFish>Rare earth weapon, very easy to cause tear damage.</entitydescription.Wf_SaltedFish>
  <entityname.Wf_Admiral_Katana>Katana</entityname.Wf_Admiral_Katana>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Katana>A melee weapon in the eastern countries of the earth, very easy to cause bloodshed</entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Katana>
  <entityname.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi>Katana</entityname.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi>A melee weapon of the countries in the east of the earth, shorter than Taidao</entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi>
  <entityname.Wf_Admiral_Katana_kai>Thermal Taichi</entityname.Wf_Admiral_Katana_kai>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Katana_kai>A modern and improved tachi made of exotic materials capable of cutting through almost any monster's armor. But the high temperature will directly heal the wound, losing the ability to bleed</entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Katana_kai>
  <entityname.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi_kai>thermal energy difference</entityname.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi_kai>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi_kai>A modernized wakizashi using exotic materials capable of cutting through almost any monster's armor. But the high temperature will directly heal the wound, losing the ability to bleed</entitydescription.Wf_Admiral_Wakizashi_kai>
  <entityname.Wf_Blame_harpoongun>Electric Harpoon Launcher</entityname.Wf_Blame_harpoongun>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Blame_harpoongun>Unidentified man-made objects brought back in the deep sea, the legendary electric-based fisherman's weapon, the harpoon launched through electromagnetic force has extremely high penetration power, and the attack power has been strengthened by 30%, which seems to be compatible with the standard batteries we use.</entitydescription.Wf_Blame_harpoongun>
  <entityname.Wf_Blame_spear>Electric Harpoon</entityname.Wf_Blame_spear>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Blame_spear>The legendary electric-based fisherman's weapon is extremely hard</entitydescription.Wf_Blame_spear>
  <entityname.Wf_Blame_batterycell>Electric Harpoon Launcher Battery</entityname.Wf_Blame_batterycell>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Blame_batterycell>The batteries that come with the electric-based harpoon launcher are not compatible with our electrical appliances and chargers, and can only be used with the electric-based harpoon launcher</entitydescription.Wf_Blame_batterycell>
  <entityname.Wf_Blame_G.B.E>graviton radiation injection device</entityname.Wf_Blame_G.B.E>
  <entitydescription.Wf_Blame_G.B.E>Graviton Beam Emitter, an extremely rare unidentified weapon found in the deep sea, is shaped like a pistol, and can emit graviton beams of different powers according to the remaining power, and generate a beam at the end of the beam that attracts surrounding objects Gravity explosion. No matter what kind of power is emitted, the graviton radiation has unparalleled power, so it needs to be used with caution</entitydescription.Wf_Blame_G.B.E>
  <entityname.Wf_G.B.E_batterycell>G.B.E Energy Unit</entityname.Wf_G.B.E_batterycell>
  <entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_batterycell>The energy unit of the graviton radiation injection device is not compatible with our electrical appliances and chargers, it is only used for the graviton radiation injection device</entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_batterycell>
  <entityname.Wf_G.B.E_kai>Microgravon Radiation Pistol</entityname.Wf_G.B.E_kai>
  <entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_kai>The alliance tried to transform the graviton radiation ejection device into a general-purpose weapon. The power is greatly reduced, but it can be compatible with Europa's general-purpose charging device</entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_kai>
  <entityname.Wf_G.B.E_kai_beam>Microgravity radiation</entityname.Wf_G.B.E_kai_beam>
  <entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_kai_beam>Microgravity radiation</entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_kai_beam>
  <entityname.Wf_G.B.E_beam_s>few gravitons</entityname.Wf_G.B.E_beam_s>
  <entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_beam_s>few gravitons</entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_beam_s>
  <entityname.Wf_G.B.E_beam_m>some gravitons</entityname.Wf_G.B.E_beam_m>
  <entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_beam_m>some gravitons</entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_beam_m>
  <entityname.Wf_G.B.E_beam_b>a large number of gravitons</entityname.Wf_G.B.E_beam_b>
  <entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_beam_b>a large number of gravitons</entitydescription.Wf_G.B.E_beam_b>
  <entityname.Wf_pucs>EPSP</entityname.Wf_pucs>
  <entitydescription.Wf_pucs>Experimental Pressure Stabilized PUCS (Experimental Pressure Stabilized PUCS): Using experimental technology, the pressure stabilizer replaces the diving suit with a thick shell, which has better vision and mobility than ordinary PUCS.</entitydescription.Wf_pucs>
  <entityname.Wf_pucs_R>Combat EPSP</entityname.Wf_pucs_R>
  <entitydescription.Wf_pucs_R>Targeted improved EPSP, using bulletproof fiber to strengthen the defense against some attacks.</entitydescription.Wf_pucs_R>
  <entityname.Wf_pucs_B>Deep dive EPSP</entityname.Wf_pucs_B>
  <entitydescription.Wf_pucs_B>The targeted improved EPSP uses bulletproof fiber and titanium-aluminum alloy to strengthen the defense. While maintaining excellent burn defense, it has the defense and pressure resistance of a standard abyss diving suit.</entitydescription.Wf_pucs_B>
  <entityname.Wf_pucs_D>Special Operations EPSP</entityname.Wf_pucs_D>
  <entitydescription.Wf_pucs_D>The targeted improved EPSP uses low-visibility paint and strengthens the defense against human weapons, and is equipped with small propellers to facilitate the rapid transfer of combatants outside the combat area.</entitydescription.Wf_pucs_D>
  <!--Short front clothing-->
  <entityname.RO635uniform1>RO635 Humanoid Costume</entityname.RO635uniform1>
  <entityname.UMP9uniform1>UMP9 Humanoid Costume</entityname.UMP9uniform1>
  <entityname.securityuniform4>midnight gospel</entityname.securityuniform4>
  <entityname.securityuniform5>MP7 Figure Costume</entityname.securityuniform5>
  <entityname.securityuniform6>VSK figure clothing</entityname.securityuniform6>
  <entityname.securityuniform7>M200 Figure Costume</entityname.securityuniform7>
  <entityname.securityuniform8>Kalina Figure Costume</entityname.securityuniform8>
  <entityname.M45uniform1>M/45 Figure Costume</entityname.M45uniform1>
  <entityname.AK12uniform>AK12 Figure Costume</entityname.AK12uniform>
  <!--Other clothing-->
  <entityname.GTCQuniform1>Gothic dress</entityname.GTCQuniform1>
  <entityname.HeiTieuniform>Black Steel Uniform-L</entityname.HeiTieuniform>
  <entityname.QPuniform>red peony</entityname.QPuniform>
  <entityname.BSQPuniform>white cheongsam</entityname.BSQPuniform>
  <entityname.ArmedJKuniform>Armed JK suit</entityname.ArmedJKuniform>
  <entityname.HeiTieuniform2>Black Steel Uniform - F</entityname.HeiTieuniform2>
  <entityname.ArmedJK_xionggua>Special Chest Hanger</entityname.ArmedJK_xionggua>
  <entitydescription.ArmedJK_xionggua>Well, the special chest hanging uses an unknown technology, in short, it can stuff a lot of things and increase your attack power at the same time</entitydescription.ArmedJK_xionggua>
  <entityname.ArmedJK_genesplicer>Custom Tactical Gene Splicer</entityname.ArmedJK_genesplicer>
  <entityname.Kaltsituniform>rhode island medical executive attire</entityname.Kaltsituniform>
  <entitydescription.Kaltsituniform>"doctor?"</entitydescription.Kaltsituniform>
  <entityname.shengxuanuniform>Shengxuan</entityname.shengxuanuniform>
  <entitydescription.shengxuanuniform>Mourn with butterflies for those who sleep</entitydescription.shengxuanuniform>
  <entityname.shengxuanhats>Funeral gift for dead butterflies</entityname.shengxuanhats>
  <entitydescription.shengxuanhats>"Where do people go after death?"</entitydescription.shengxuanhats>
  <entityname.succubusmask>Succubus Mask</entityname.succubusmask>
  <entitydescription.succubusmask>“Great, just what I needed”</entitydescription.succubusmask>
  <entityname.succubussuit>Succubus set</entityname.succubussuit>
  <entitydescription.succubussuit>A clown who signs a contract with the devil will eventually become a succubus. "No, it's illogical"</entitydescription.succubussuit>
  <entityname.tight_combatsuit_1>tight combat suit mk1</entityname.tight_combatsuit_1>
  <entitydescription.tight_combatsuit_1>Outline your beautiful figure</entitydescription.tight_combatsuit_1>
  <entityname.tight_combatsuit_2>tight combat suit mk2</entityname.tight_combatsuit_2>
  <entitydescription.tight_combatsuit_2>Outline your beautiful figure</entitydescription.tight_combatsuit_2>
  <entityname.whiteswimmingsuit>White Competitive Swimsuit</entityname.whiteswimmingsuit>
  <entitydescription.whiteswimmingsuit>Wear it to compete with the seafood</entitydescription.whiteswimmingsuit>
  <entityname.blue_combatsuit>blue battle suit</entityname.blue_combatsuit>
  <entitydescription.blue_combatsuit>It looks sexier from the front than from the side. (Don't tilt your head to look at the screen, invisible)</entitydescription.blue_combatsuit>
  <entityname.guardiansuit>Guardian battle suit</entityname.guardiansuit>
  <entitydescription.guardiansuit>Someone wore it and the armor was torn apart, now you wear it and drive a submarine</entitydescription.guardiansuit>
  <entityname.Sailor_suit>sailor suit</entityname.Sailor_suit>
  <entitydescription.Sailor_suit>is the feeling of youth</entitydescription.Sailor_suit>
  <entityname.White_meteor>pure white meteor</entityname.White_meteor>
  <entitydescription.White_meteor>Meteor in the daytime, go forward with your wish!</entitydescription.White_meteor>
  <entityname.Sports_shorts>sports Shorts</entityname.Sports_shorts>
  <entitydescription.Sports_shorts>exercise, defend yourself</entitydescription.Sports_shorts>
  <entityname.Competitive_swimsuit>Backless Competitive Swimsuit</entityname.Competitive_swimsuit>
  <entitydescription.Competitive_swimsuit>Compete with tiger tail sharks to see who is faster</entitydescription.Competitive_swimsuit>
  <entityname.Exotic_Amor_suit>Exotic Matter Armor - Diving Suit</entityname.Exotic_Amor_suit>
  <entitydescription.Exotic_Amor_suit>This is the wetsuit part of the suit, which is made of the alien material extracted from the biological crust of Europa. Collecting all the parts of the set will give you a higher bonus. (WIP)</entitydescription.Exotic_Amor_suit>
  <entityname.Exotic_Amor_suit_head>Exotic Matter Armor - Helmet</entityname.Exotic_Amor_suit_head>
  <entitydescription.Exotic_Amor_suit_head>This is the helmet part of the suit, which is made of the alien material extracted from the biological carapace of Europa. Collecting all the parts of the set will give you a higher bonus. (WIP)</entitydescription.Exotic_Amor_suit_head>
  <entityname.PrayerMio_uniform>HGIS</entityname.PrayerMio_uniform>
  <entitydescription.PrayerMio_uniform>Experimental protective clothing and matching armor used by the Mars UAC Research Institute for subspace exploration research. A high-performance suit designed to protect the wearer in harsh environments. [Clothing part] "Contribution from Chiyo Mio, the up master of station b" (WIP)</entitydescription.PrayerMio_uniform>
  <entityname.PrayerMio_hat>prism</entityname.PrayerMio_hat>
  <entitydescription.PrayerMio_hat>The experimental protective clothing and matching armor used by the Mars UAC Research Institute for subspace exploration research. A high-performance suit designed to protect the wearer in harsh environments. [Crown ring part] "Contribution from Chiyo Mio, the up master of station b" (WIP)</entitydescription.PrayerMio_hat>
  <entityname.IronArmourPlus>Armor but better I guess</entityname.IronArmourPlus>
  <entitydescription.IronArmourPlus>After some bored crew forged the Mechanic's makeshift armor. Don't think this is cool? It fits my vision of a Europa submarine in the 22nd century. (WIP)</entitydescription.IronArmourPlus>
  <!--EA-HI item-->
  <entityname.EAHI_pucs>[EA-HI] PUCS</entityname.EAHI_pucs>
  <entitydescription.EAHI_pucs>Donga Heavy Industries PUCS, using the next generation outrageous technology, to prevent your beautiful face and slender legs from being covered. An integrated compressor automatically extracts oxygen from the air. Withstand up to 8000 meters of water pressure.</entitydescription.EAHI_pucs>
  <entityname.EAHI_autoinjectorheadset>[EA-HI] Self-injecting earphones</entityname.EAHI_autoinjectorheadset>
  <entitydescription.EAHI_autoinjectorheadset>The integrated self-injection earphone developed by East Asia Heavy Industries has a health scanner function and a built-in authority simulation system that can crack most alliance insurance</entitydescription.EAHI_autoinjectorheadset>
  <entityname.EAHI_pulselaserammobox>[EA-HI] Durable Laser Supply Box</entityname.EAHI_pulselaserammobox>
  <entitydescription.EAHI_pulselaserammobox>Durable Laser, with armor-piercing capabilities and greater capacity. Of course, correspondingly, lower damage.</entitydescription.EAHI_pulselaserammobox>
  <entityname.EAHI_kuorongbag>[EA-HI] Prototype Expansion Pack</entityname.EAHI_kuorongbag>
  <entitydescription.EAHI_kuorongbag>The general expansion package developed by East Asia Heavy Industries was cut in half due to infringement issues. A small pouch that can be installed in the inventory, and can also be loaded into a gun to increase the charge capacity of revolvers, harpoons, shotguns, hand cannons, and stun guns</entitydescription.EAHI_kuorongbag>
  <entityname.EAHI_handheldsonar>[EA-HI] Advanced Sonar</entityname.EAHI_handheldsonar>
  <entitydescription.EAHI_handheldsonar>High-power sonar, can penetrate the hull of the submarine, a must for gunners</entitydescription.EAHI_handheldsonar>
  <entityname.EAHI_duogongnengtool>[EA-HI] Prototype Multi-Tool</entityname.EAHI_duogongnengtool>
  <entitydescription.EAHI_duogongnengtool>The multi-function tool developed by East Asia Heavy Industries has stopped production due to the high cost. This tool is a screwdriver, wrench, welding tool, mining tool all in one. Powered by high pressure gas. Note: AI cannot use</entitydescription.EAHI_duogongnengtool>
  <entityname.teleportine>[EA-HI] Teleport Potion</entityname.teleportine>
  <entitydescription.teleportine>The teleportation potion distributed by East Asia Heavy Industries to the liaison officers of each site will quickly teleport him to a safe place when the liaison officer is injured.</entitydescription.teleportine>
  <entityname.exotic_matter>Exotic matter</entityname.exotic_matter>
  <entitydescription.exotic_matter>Exotic matter extracted from Europa's bio-carapace possesses rather ingenious properties.</entitydescription.exotic_matter>
  <entityname.EAHI_license_oneoff>Master Blueprint - [type]</entityname.EAHI_license_oneoff>
  <entitydescription.EAHI_licence_oneoff>Put the blueprint and corresponding items into the 3D printer of Dongya Heavy Industries, you can improve the production level of the corresponding items</entitydescription.EAHI_licence_oneoff>
  <!--Talent-->
  <talentname.wf_researcher></talentname.wf_researcher>
  <!--AFF-->
  <Builder.Msg.Detach>[[use]] Detatch</Builder.Msg.Detach>
  <!--eventtext-->
  <EventText.missionevent_EAHI1.c1>Loafer[East Asia heavy industry liaison officer]: Zzz. This is your task, don't disturb my sleep.</EventText.missionevent_EAHI1.c1>
  <EventText.missionevent_EAHI2.c1>Chao Wendao [East Asia Heavy Industry entrusted person in charge]: Are you here to accept the entrustment? OK, there are two tasks here.</EventText.missionevent_EAHI2.c1>
  <EventText.missionevent_XML.c1>A liaison officer from East Asia Heavy Industries said that recently a group of particularly ferocious Velociraptors was attacking ships traveling in the waterway, seriously affecting the interests of the company. [reward]mk has been promised to those who annihilate this horde of monsters. "</EventText.missionevent_XML.c1>
  <EventText.missionevent_PP.c1>The Mother of Many Creepers leads hordes of Creepers to attack ships in the channel. East Asia Heavy Industries promises to give [reward]mk rewards to those who annihilate this group of monsters.</EventText.missionevent_PP.c1>
  <EventText.missionevent_HF.c1>A large number of golden hammerheads are entrenched in the waterway, seriously affecting the transportation of people and goods. East Asia Heavy Industries is offering a reward [reward]mk to all free captains in order to solve this problem.</EventText.missionevent_HF.c1>
  <EventText.missionevent_MLK.c1>"A horde of aggressive molroks is attacking ships traveling between [location1] and [location2]. A [reward]mk has been promised to whoever annihilates the horde."</EventText.missionevent_MLK.c1>
  <EventText.missionevent_SY.c1>East Asia Heavy Industries' illegal experiment in the abyss alarmed the Destruction Worm. The liaison officer hopes that you can defeat the Worm before it is discovered by the Alliance, otherwise East Asia Heavy Industries will face a large fine.</EventText.missionevent_SY.c1>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YMLKR>tobacco mania</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YMLKR>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YMLKR>East Asia Heavy Industries recently ordered a large amount of tobacco, but due to the alliance's embargo on strategic materials, it could not be delivered, and the site was checking for contraband. In order to prevent exposure, the liaison officer asked you to help deliver a batch of goods. "Wait, when did tobacco become illegal?"</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YMLKR>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YMLKR>"Tobacco" has been successfully delivered to [location2]</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YMLKR>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_YMLKR>Obviously, this is not tobacco at all, but a mutated Bomb Fruit</missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_YMLKR>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>Radiation Sapper</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>【warn! Bad file risk] The liaison officer entrusted you to deliver a batch of high-risk volatile ratin fuel, and gave [reward]mk, you think about it, it is nothing more than radiation sickness. "How can my life be more important than money?"</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>Volatile Rexon Fuel Rods have been successfully delivered to [location2]</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>Brother, you have to spend your money wisely.</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_FXGB>
  <missionname.EAHI_Mission_ZBKC>Explosive Truck</missionname.EAHI_Mission_ZBKC>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_ZBKC>【warn! Bad file risk] The liaison officer entrusted you to deliver a batch of high-risk volatile azide compounds, and gave [reward] mk. 【The entrustment must be delivered within 10 minutes, otherwise the consequences will be at your own risk】</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_ZBKC>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_ZBKC>You breathe a sigh of relief that the volatile azide has been successfully delivered to [location2].</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_ZBKC>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_ZBKC>Brother, you have to spend your money wisely.</missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_ZBKC>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>luck or return</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>The liaison officer entrusted you to deliver a batch of alliance medals, and gave [reward]mk. "I hope you don't use it yourself," the liaison officer said, "Even if you use it yourself, I can't do anything about it."</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>It's incredible that you restrained your greed</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>"I knew it," said the liaison officer.</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_1>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>luck or return</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>The liaison officer entrusted you to deliver a batch of endocrine enhancer, and gave [reward]mk. "I hope you don't use it yourself," the liaison officer said, "Even if you use it yourself, I can't do anything about it."</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>It's incredible that you restrained your greed</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>"I knew it," said the liaison officer.</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>luck or return</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>The liaison officer entrusted you to deliver a batch of skill books, and gave [reward]mk. "I hope you don't use it yourself," the liaison officer said, "Even if you use it yourself, I can't do anything about it."</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>It's incredible that you restrained your greed</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>"I knew it," said the liaison officer.</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_YYWH_2>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>rubbish truck</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>The liaison entrusts you to deliver a scrap [reward]mk</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>Scrap has been successfully delivered to [location2]</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>No way, why would someone be short of scraps?</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_LJC>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>clothing transportation</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>The liaison entrusts you to deliver a garment [reward]mk</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>Clothing has been successfully delivered to [location2]</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>No way, why would someone be short of clothes?</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_FZ>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>small movie</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>In view of Europa's poor network environment, the liaison officer asks you to help him bring a batch of goods, mainly hard drives. "It's all confidential documents, don't flip through them," said the liaison officer. [reward]mk</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>You look through the logs and don't find what you're looking for. Anyway, the things have been delivered anyway, so what the heck.</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>How did you fail? There's no shortage of short films, is there?</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XDY>
  <missionname.EAHI_Mission_PPQY>Prosperity</missionname.EAHI_Mission_PPQY>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>East Asia Heavy Industries entrusts you to assassinate a senior official of the alliance who hinders the company's interests. If you succeed, you will be given [reward]mk. Please bide your time, clear them all, and throw the bodies overboard.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>"It's not surprising what happens in the deep sea, is it?"</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_PPQY>You killed the senior officer at the wrong time, allowing him to send a distress message</missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_PPQY>
  <missionheader0.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>mission failed</missionheader0.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>
  <missionmessage0.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>You killed the senior officer at the wrong time, allowing him to send a distress message</missionmessage0.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>
  <missionheader1.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>successful assassination</missionheader1.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>
  <missionmessage1.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>You got your timing and killed the top officer in the comms blind spot</missionmessage1.EAHI_Misssion_PPQY>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_PP>Mother of the Creepers Annihilation</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_PP>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_PP>The Mother of Many Creepers leads hordes of Creepers to attack ships in the channel. East Asia Heavy Industries promised to give 8,500 mk rewards to those who wiped out this group of monsters.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_PP>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_PP>Colonies of algae crawlers have been removed</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_PP>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_PP>Algal crawler colonies not removed</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_PP>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XML>Velociraptor Fight</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XML>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XML>A liaison officer from East Asia Heavy Industries said that recently a group of particularly ferocious Velociraptors was attacking ships traveling in the waterway, seriously affecting the interests of the company. A reward of 8000mk has been promised to whoever annihilates this horde of monsters.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XML>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XML>Velociraptor herd has been cleared</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XML>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XML>Velociraptor herd not cleared</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XML>
  <missionname.EAHI_Mission_HF>golden wind</missionname.EAHI_Mission_HF>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_HF>A large number of golden hammerheads are entrenched in the waterway, seriously affecting the transportation of people and goods. East Asia Heavy Industries is offering a reward of 9000mk to all free captains in order to solve this problem.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_HF>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_HF>The golden storm has died down</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_HF>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_HF>The golden storm is still raging</missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_HF>
  <missionname.EAHI_Mission_MLKQ>Hunting the Molroks</missionname.EAHI_Mission_MLKQ>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_MLKQ>A group of extremely powerful molroks are attacking the ships traveling in the channel. A reward of 10000mk has been promised to those who annihilate this group of monsters.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_MLKQ>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_MLKQ>Morox group has been cleared</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_MLKQ>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_MLKQ>Morox not cleared</missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_MLKQ>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_HMLK>dark clouds</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_HMLK>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_HMLK>A group of extremely aggressive black molroks are attacking the ships traveling in the channel. A reward of 10000mk has been promised to those who annihilate this group of monsters.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_HMLK>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_HMLK>The black molrox group has been cleared</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_HMLK>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_HMLK>Black molrox group not cleared</missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_HMLK>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>illegal experiment</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>East Asia Heavy Industries' illegal experiment in the abyss alarmed the Destruction Worm. The liaison officer hopes that you can defeat the Worm before it is discovered by the Alliance, otherwise East Asia Heavy Industries will face a large fine.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>The worm has been killed</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>The worm was not killed</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_1>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>illegal experiment</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>East Asia Heavy Industries' illegal experiment in the abyss alarmed the Banshee, and the liaison officer hopes that you can defeat the Banshee before it is discovered by the alliance, otherwise East Asia Heavy Industries will face a large fine.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>Banshee has been killed</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>Banshee not killed</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_2>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>illegal experiment</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>【warn! Difficult task] Dongya Heavy Industries' illegal experiment in the abyss has alarmed the doomsday worm. The liaison officer hopes that you can defeat the worm before it is discovered by the alliance, otherwise Dongya Heavy Industries will face a large fine.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>The worm has been killed</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>The worm was not killed</missionfailure.EAHI_Misssion_XFFSY_3>
  <missionname.EAHI_Misssion_JGHX>"Quiet" to watch a good show</missionname.EAHI_Misssion_JGHX>
  <missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_JGHX>The Liaison invites you to a good show, the showdown of the century between Hammerhead and the Sea Eater. "Remember to remain silent," said the liaison officer.</missiondescription.EAHI_Misssion_JGHX>
  <missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_JGHX>It was brilliant, it's a pity someone has to clean up the mess.</missionsuccess.EAHI_Misssion_JGHX>
  <missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_JGHX>You failed to keep silent and got caught up in the fray</missionfailure.EAHI_Mission_JGHX>
</infotexts>